kkday.com 2019-05-17

# Terms and privacy

In Accordance to “Personal Information Protection Act” of Taiwan and EU GDPR or Personal Data of (Privacy) Ordinance of HK or Personal Data Protection Act(PDPA) of SG or other related legal regulations in each country, KKday is committed to protecting privacy of your personal data with utmost sincerity. KKday will inform you regarding the purpose of collecting and the range for using of your personal information which is collected when you sign up to be KKday’s member to buy our tour packages or other goods on KKday website and APP. As a consumer, you will be provided full knowledge on the purpose of each personal information collected as you sign up to be a KKday member. Doing so will allow you to purchase our tour packages and other goods on the KKday website and application. KKday expects you to understand your related rights so as to feel comfortable to use all related Internet services provided by KKday. KKday will uphold your rights as a consumer to ensure your confidence in using all internet-related services provided by KKday.com. 

In order to fully provide our service to you, we will be collecting your personal information through the following methods. It may be done through certain parts of KKday website (when registering or while using the function of “Message” of KKday website), KKday APP, or KKday Service Center (via E-mail or telephone). You will be asked to provide personal identification information which includes but will not limited to following categories. Doing so, to grant you access to certain parts of the website and application, allowing you to make use of the services KKday provides: 

  * (1).Sign up to be a KKday member
  * (2).Purchase tour package or tickets, sim cards, WiFi router rental
  * (3).Provide your personal information and contact methods for KKday or suppliers to prepare or prearrange tour packages or other goods
  * (4).Using the KKday member’s exclusive interaction service
  * (5).Receive newest KKday’s recommendation, promotion information or other EDM

KKday will collect your personal information for specific purposes, which you may see below: 

  * 【Sign up process】your name、your nationality、your resident、your phone number、your contact E-mail、your date of birth、your gender.
  * 【Booking process】your credit card number (Cardholder name、Credit card number、Expiration date、CVC/CVV)、your information of other on-line payment methods (Android Pay or LINE Pay). Sometimes you will have to provide us your name on your passport as well as passport number after booking tour packages There will be instances wherein you will have to provide us your name as displayed in your passport, as well as your passport number, depending on the needs of each product. You will have to provide us your resident address if you choose to book goods which you hope we deliver to you. 

If you didn’t provide us complete information or if you provide wrong information to KKday, KKday may not be able to prepare/prearrange or deliver goods (SIMCards、WiFi Router、Tickets and Passes) to you. As a consumer, you are responsible in providing complete and accurate information as requested by KKday. Inability to do so may lead to errors in your order, which may lead to lost packages or canceled tours. The customers’ personal information gathered by KKday will be used for the sole purpose of providing our service in the best of our abilities. It will be utilized in order to improve our services, and to provide a more personalized customer experience. 

KKday may have to provide your information to our subsidiaries or our KKday’s suppliers or Credit Card Associations and banks. Without your prior consent, KKday promises that KKday won’t use your personal information in the purpose which is not related to your booking. KKday won’t provide your personal information to any third party expect KKday and related services providers. As a service, KKday may disclose your information to our subsidiaries, and/or our suppliers, and/or credit card associations, and/or banks. Without your prior consent, KKday will not make use of your personal information in a purpose which is not related to your order. KKday will not disclose your personal information to any third party except for the related services providers. 

After providing your personal information above, if you want to change your information, you can sign up to our system to revise or update your information. If you hope that KKday revise or amend or delete your personal information, please contact us and provide your opinion to our customer service center:  
E-mail of our service center: service@kkday.com  
contact phone: +886-2-7741-7450  
Mobile phone: +886-0971-532-770  
Fax: +886-2-2786-1101  
After receiving your opinion, KKday will deliver your requestment and opinion to our IT department immediately. We will inform you processing status and results instantly. 

KKday may gather your IP address to identify your location when you are browsing KKday website. KKday may also gather “Cookies”, a small piece of data sent from the website and stored on the user's computer which tracks the users browsing activity within the KKday website. KKday may use “Cookies” to record the user's browsing activity (including but not limited to - the links selected, the period of use, and a record of the pages visited in the past). KKday may use your IP address records and data collected by cookies or other browsing-related behavior to record and analyze the users’ preference, or to develop business and marketing strategies done to improve or maintain quality of service or introduce packages or goods to you. When KKday analyzes the user’s data and browsing behavior collected, KKday guarantees that it will only be used to predict business trends and acquire the users’ habit and preference. KKday will not use the data and information gathered to identify or jeopardize the privacy of the customer. 

The personal information shared to KKday will be kept until it is no longer needed or up until the period stipulated by law. You have the right to revise, delete, view, supply, and apply for a portable copy of your personal information under the specific provisions of the “Personal Information Protection Act” or EU GDPR or Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap. 486) of HK or Personal Data Protection Act(PDPA) of SG. There will be circumstances wherein KKday may provide your information to a third party or government units. These circumstances include the following: 

  * (a).An ordered legal requirement from government units or judicial institutions.
  * (b).If it can be used to protect one’s personal safety according to KKday’s rational judgment.
  * (c).If the information collected by KKday may be related to illegal activities or violations affecting the public’s interest and good customs.

The privacy policy will only be applicable within the domain of KKday.com. KKday will not be liable to links within the website directing to other domains. We highly recommend you to view the privacy policies of other websites for your reference. We will not be able to assure the security of your personal information if shared in other domains outside KKday.com. 

Any dispute arising out of or in connection with this website shall be governed and construed by the laws of the Republic of China, and shall be resolved by Taiwan Taipei District Court which serves as the court of first instance.  
Any dispute arising out of or in connection with this website (HK Version) shall be governed and construed by the laws of Hong Kong. 

Please contact us if you have any questions regarding KKday’s Privacy Policy via KKday’s Customer Service Center “e-mail: service@kkday.com”. KKday will answer your request and reply you immediately.
